

PETRA KOLARIČ

ABOUT ME

Open for #NewChallenge

Based on past working experience, I am aware of priorities that must be completed in a timely manner. I am respectful, reliable, confident, and communicative. Task-oriented, team player, and great at finding convenient solutions. Always with a positive attitude, adaptable to implement various tasks.

+386 31 308 812

Slovenia, Europe

petra.kolaricc@gmail.com

www.petrakolaric.com

REFERENCES

PRODUCT MANAGER (MPG)
VOLUNTEER (NGO Andromeda)

INTERESTS

NEW KNOWLEDGE ART, AI, TECH, MARKETING

LANGUAGES

SLOVENE
ENGLISH
CROATIAN
ITALIAN
GERMAN

EDUCATION

BA Fashion Designer

Faculty of design / Ljubljana, Slovenia

EXPERIENCE

PRODUCT MANAGER
10DX GROUP Ltd. / Maribor, Slovenia

12/2020 - present

Marketing agency 10DX GROUP Ltd. specializes in eCommerce and performance digital marketing. Present on EU and US markets.

Managing product entries and product descriptions, control of orderliness of websites, proofreading, timeliness of information, price list control, checking the accuracy of stocks, communication with

suppliers, tracking delivery deadline, coordination of offers.

PRODUCT MANAGER

12/2016 - 12/2019

Michael Pachleitner Group / Graz, Austria

Optics company with headquarters in Graz. Design and trading of an extensive range of frame brands, sunglasses, eyeglass lenses, and jewelry designed in Austria.

Market and competition research, tracking and forecasting fashion trends. Collecting relevant ideas, color combinations, materials, and selecting suppliers for future collections.

Preparation of technical packages, sending inquiries, offers, orders, and taking into account delivery deadlines.

Organization, coordination of meetings and participation in business trips, visiting suppliers abroad, optical and fashion fairs.

ART EVENT MANAGER Igrajmo se IC / Ptuj, Slovenia

10/2010 - 11/2016

Organization of cultural events in a fast-paced work environment. Involved and worked in creative workshops, fashion shows, outdoor events, musical and theater performances, promotions, team building activities, conferences, weddings, etc.

Worked as a student and in March 2016, became a full-time employee. Involved in the entire event planning process, preparing and implementing cultural events from inquiry to realization.

ASSISTANT OF BRAND MANAGER EUROPA 92 Ltd. / Zagreb, Croatia

8/2015 - 2/2016

Europe 92 - the largest Jeans clothing retailer in Croatia.

Worked in the design department, providing statistics and documentation to other departments.

Providing reports technical drawings and packages, preparing materials, mood boards and colors in Adobe Illustrator and Corel Draw. Product management up to the last step in the production and control of the collection in actual shops.

SKILLS

MICROSOFT OFFICE SUITE
ADOBE ILLUSTRATOR & PHOTOSHOP
ERP SYSTEM (SAP)
WORDPRESS, SHOPIFY
COPYWRITING

